Guide to the Kay Thode Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Kay Thode papers, 1962-2003; 5353-003; 3.64 cubic feet 4 boxes and 1 oversize folder
  - Washington State Friends of Welfare Rights, 1964-1975; Series 10
    - Subject File: Elaine McLean
      - Newsletters
        - The Welfare Fighter(National Welfare Rights Organization), 1971 (Box-folder:oversize Miscellaneous Oversize Box 10)
        - Adequate Income Newsletter(California Welfare Rights Organization), 1971 (Box-folder:oversize Miscellaneous Oversize Box 10)
      - Drawings, undated (Box-folder 4/22)
      - Clippings (Box-folder 4/23)
    - Clippings, 1969-1972, undated (Box-folder 4/24)
    - Notes, 1971-1972, undated (Box-folder 4/25)
    - Ephemera
      - Washington State Welfare Rights Organization, 1964, 1970, undated (Box-folder 4/26)
      - National Welfare Rights Organization, 1968, 1970, undated (Box-folder 4/27)
      - Miscellaneous, 1970-1972, undated (Box-folder 4/28)
- Kay Thode papers, 1974-1987; 5353-004; 0.36 cubic feet (1 box)
  Fact sheets, white papers, reports, news clippings, photographs and lobbying materials that Kay Thode created and collected in her role as a lobbyist in the Washington State Legislature for the Urban League on behalf of antipoverty and welfare iniatives. Materials also relate to Thode's work as the Director of Health and Welfare for the Seattle Urban League.
  No restrictions on access.
  Kay Thode via Margaret Casey, 2016
  - Photographs, undated (Box-folder 1/1)
  - Draft of an open letter to the Governor and legislature re: children and poverty, 1985 (Box-folder 1/2)
  - Testimony on poverty, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 1/3)
  - Work, welfare, women and wealth, or whose work and whose welfare, 1977 (Box-folder 1/4)
    Paper presented by Kay Thode to the Washington Association of Social Welfare Conference on October 24, 1977.
  - Poverty -- work and welfare, 1969-1978 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Review of standards for grant assistance, 1975 (Box-folder 1/6)
    Published by the Department of Social and Health Sciences Planning and Research Division, Office of Program Analysis and Standards, Olympia, Washington, October 1975
  - Women and the Law conference, 1981 (Box-folder 1/7-8)
    Materials relating to the 11th Far West Regional Conference on Women & the Law in October of 1981 included a panel presentation Kay Thode was part of.
  - Uncompensated care: A major ethical issue, 1984 (Box-folder 1/9-10)
    This publication was prepared by Kay Thode for the King County Health Planning Council, May 1984
  - Governor's conference on health care financing: perpectives for the 1980's, 1982 (Box-folder 1/11-12)
    Materials related to the conference including preceedings and Kay Thode's drafts of presentations.